<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="ca.maestrosoft.eclipse.feature.studio"
      label="Maestrosoft Technologies C/C++ Studio"
      version="9.0.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="Maestrosoft Technologies"
      plugin="ca.maestrosoft.eclipse.cdt.plugin.studio"
      os="win32"
      ws="win32"
      arch="x86,x86_64">

   <description>
      Maestrosoft Technologies Eclipse C/C++ Studio
   </description>

   <copyright url="copyright.htm">
      MAESTROSOFT TECHNOLOGIES PROPRIETARY INFORMATION 
This software is supplied under the terms of a license agreement
or non disclosure agreement with Maestrosoft Technologies and
may not be copied or disclosed except in accordance with the 
terms of that agreement. 
Copyright(c) 2014 Maestrosoft technologies All Rights Reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license url="license.htm">
      MAESTROSOFT TECHNOLOGIES END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT

NOTICE TO USERS: CAREFULLY READ THE FOLLOWING LEGAL AGREEMENT. USE OF THE 
SOFTWARE PROVIDED WITH THIS AGREEMENT (THE &quot;SOFTWARE&quot;) CONSTITUTES YOUR 
ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS 
AGREEMENT, DO NOT INSTALL AND/OR USE THIS SOFTWARE. USER&apos;S USE OF THIS 
SOFTWARE IS CONDITIONED UPON COMPLIANCE BY USER WITH THE TERMS OF THIS 
AGREEMENT. 


COPYRIGHT/OWNERSHIP

The Software and its source code, any accompanying printed materials and 
all copies of the Software and printed materials are proprietary products 
owned and copyrighted by MaestrosoftTechnologies and are protected by 
copyright, trademark and trade secret laws and international treaty 
provisions. The Software is licensed and not sold. Your License confers 
no title or ownership in the Software and should not be construed as a 
sale of any right in the Software. You acknowledge that no title to the 
intellectual property in the Software is transferred to you. You further 
acknowledge that title and full ownership rights to the Software will 
remain the exclusive property of MaestrosoftTechnologies and you will not 
acquire any rights to the Software except as expressly set forth in this 
License. You agree that any copies of the Software will contain the same 
proprietary notices which appear on and in the Software.

The Licensee may not use, copy, emulate, reproduce, clone, rent, lease, 
sell, sublicense, translate, modify, decompile, disassemble, otherwise 
reverse engineer, extract images, sounds, texts, or transfer the licensed 
program, or any subset of the licensed program, adapt or create derived 
works based on the Software or documentation, in whole or in part, for 
any purpose and in any manner. Any such unauthorized use shall result in 
immediate and automatic termination of this License and may result in 
criminal and/or civil prosecution. 


GRANT AND RESPONSIBILITIES OF LICENSEE

MaestrosoftTechnologies grants you a non-exclusive license to use this 
Software, and any associated documentation, as indicated herein. If you 
have purchased a Single User License, one copy of the Software may be 
installed and used, for internal use only, on a single computer. The 
Software is in &quot;use&quot; on a single computer when it has been loaded into 
temporary memory (i.e. RAM) or installed into permanent memory (hard disk 
or other device) of that computer. The Licensee may not make any 
unauthorized copies of the Software, except that the Licensee may make 
either one copy of the Software solely for backup or archival purposes or 
transfer the Software to a single hard disk provided you keep the 
original solely for backup or archival purposes.


TERM

This License is effective until terminated. You may terminate it at any 
time by destroying the Software, together with all copies thereof. This 
License will also terminate if you fail to comply with any term or 
condition of this Agreement. Upon such termination, you agree to destroy 
the Software, together with all copies thereof.


SOFTWARE TRIAL VERSION (UNACTIVATED)

The Software includes protection mechanisms to prevent the use of the 
Software after the trial evaluation period unless the appropriate 
password (activation code) is entered. Licensee rights to use any part of 
the Software after the expiration of the evaluation period is subject to 
the payment of all applicable fees and registering as a user. 
Unregistered use of this Software after the trial evaluation period is in 
violation of copyright laws. 


TRIAL VERSION DISTRIBUTION

You are hereby licensed to make as many copies of the Trial Version (and 
ONLY this version) as you wish and distribute it to anyone provided that 
all files are not modified. 

No person or company may charge a fee for the distribution of the Trial 
Version without written permission from the copyright holder. You are not 
allowed to sell the Trial Version (except for shipment and handling 
charges).

You MAY: (a) install and use the unactivated Software (Trial Version) for 
evaluation purpose only during 15 days after the installation; (b) 
provide copies of the unactivated Software to others by any mean (Cover 
Disc, CD-ROM, DVD, Web site...) for their evaluation use so long as you: 
1) provide exact, unmodified copies of the unactivated Software received 
from MaestrosoftTechnologies, including all accompanying files, this 
agreement, and all copyright, trademark, proprietary, and other notices; 
2) do not charge or collect any monetary or other compensation for or in 
connection with MaestrosoftTechnologies; 3) reference 
MaestrosoftTechnologies as the sole source of the Software.

You MAY NOT: (a) upload the Trial Version in any peer-to-peer or file 
sharing websites; (b) place anywhere a link to a page of a peer-to-peer 
or file sharing websites containing the Trial Version.


TRIAL VERSION RESTRICTIONS

You MAY NOT: (a) use the Trial Version after the evaluation period of 15 
days; (b) sell this Trial Version package; (c) cause or permit reverse 
engineering, disassemble, decompilation or alteration of this Software; 
(d) remove any product identification, copyright notices, or other 
notices or proprietary restrictions from this Software; (e) copy the 
documentation accompanying the Software.


ACTIVATED VERSION OF THE SOFTWARE

You MAY: (a) make a copy of the software for archival purpose only; 


ACTIVATED VERSION RESTRICTIONS

You MAY NOT: (a) copy, upload and distribute anywhere the Software or any 
portion of it; (b) place anywhere a link to a page containing the 
activated version of the Software; (c) sublicense, lease, rent, or 
transfer this Software to another; (d) cause or permit reverse 
engineering, disassemble, decompilation or alteration of this Software; 
(e) remove any product identification, copyright notices, or other 
notices or proprietary restrictions from this Software; (f) copy the 
documentation accompanying the Software. 


NO REFUNDS

Licensee warrants that he inspected The Software according and that it is 
adequate to his needs. Accordingly, as The Software is intangible goods, 
Licensee shall not be, ever, entitled to any refund, rebate, compensation 
or restitution for any reason whatsoever, even if The Software contains 
material flaws.


SUPPORT

Software is provided under an &quot;AS-IS&quot; basis and without any support, 
updates or maintenance. Nothing in this Agreement shall require 
MaestrosoftTechnologies to provide Licensee with support or fixes to any 
bug, failure, mis-performance or other defect in The Software.


BUG NOTIFICATION

Licensee may provide MaestrosoftTechnologies of details regarding any 
bug, defect or failure in The Software promptly and with no delay from 
such event; Licensee shall comply with Licensor&apos;s request for information 
regarding bugs, defects or failures and furnish him with information, 
screenshots and try to reproduce such bugs, defects or failures.


FEATURE REQUEST

Licensee may request additional features in Software, provided, however, 
that (i) Licensee shall waive any claim or right in such feature should 
feature be developed by Licensor; (ii) Licensee shall be prohibited from 
developing the feature, or disclose such feature request, or feature, to 
any 3rd party directly competing with Licensor or any 3rd party which may 
be, following the development of such feature, in direct competition with 
Licensor; (iii) Licensee warrants that feature does not infringe any 3rd 
party patent, trademark, trade-secret or any other intellectual property 
right; and (iv) Licensee developed, envisioned or created the feature 
solely by himself.


DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER 
EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED 
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND 
NONINFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS, OR OF ANY OTHER TYPE, WHETHER 
EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, AND TO ANY REMEDY AGAINST THE DISTRIBUTOR AND/OR 
ITS LICENSORS, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE. MAESTROSOFT 
TECHNOLOGIES DOES NOT WARRANT, GUARANTEE OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS THAT 
THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE SOFTWARE WILL MEET THE LICENSEE&apos;S 
REQUIREMENTS OR THAT THE OPERATION OF THE SOFTWARE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED 
OR ERROR-FREE. THE USER MUST ASSUME THE ENTIRE RISK OF USING THE 
SOFTWARE. IN ANY EVENT, THE DISTRIBUTOR&apos;S LIABILITY SHALL NOT EXCEED THE 
AMOUNT THE LICENSEE ORIGINALLY PAID FOR THE SOFTWARE. 


NO LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES

THE LICENSEE AGREES THAT NEITHER THE DISTRIBUTOR NOR ITS EMPLOYEES, 
MANAGEMENT, OR ANYONE ELSE WHO HAS BEEN INVOLVED IN THE CREATION, 
PRODUCTION OR DELIVERY OF THE SOFTWARE SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, 
INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING WITHOUT 
LIMITATION, LOSS OF PROFITS, REVENUE, DATA OR USE, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, 
LOSS OR INACCURACY OF INFORMATION) INCURRED BY THE LICENSEE OR ANY THIRD 
PARTY IN CONNECTION WITH OR ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF THE SOFTWARE, EVEN 
IF THE DISTRIBUTOR HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. 
ANY LIABILITY OF THE SELLER WILL BE LIMITED TO REFUND THE PURCHASE PRICE.


TERMINATION OF LICENSE

The License will terminate automatically if the Licensee fails to comply 
with any provisions of the License or upon transfer of the Software and 
documentation.


ACKNOWLEDGMENT

The Licensee acknowledges that the Licensee has read the Agreement in 
full, has fully understood its terms and agrees to be bound thereby. The 
Agreement contains the complete and exclusive agreement between the 
parties and supersedes all proposals or prior agreements, oral or 
written, and any other communications between the parties and supersedes 
all proposals or prior agreements, oral and written, and any other 
communications between the parties relating to the subject matter of the 
Agreement.
   </license>

   <includes
         id="ca.maestrosoft.cdt.patch.9.0.0"
         version="9.0.0.qualifier"
         name="Patch for CDT"/>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.core" version="6.0.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.managedbuilder.core" version="8.5.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.managedbuilder.ui" version="9.0.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.ui" version="6.0.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.filesystem" version="1.6.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources" version="3.11.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime" version="3.12.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.variables" version="3.3.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui" version="3.108.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide" version="3.12.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import feature="org.eclipse.cdt.platform" version="9.0.0.201606062011" match="perfect"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="ca.maestrosoft.eclipse.cdt.plugin.studio"
         os="win32"
         ws="win32"
         arch="x86,x86_64"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
